Oh, 8...
I searched a little bit, and I found out that there's a spell in Dracula called "Pulpute", but I don't know what happens when you use it.
When you use it, you don't know what happens... there's a recovery spell, but when you use Pulpute, you suddenly move instantly or become very strong...
That's what Pulpute is. Why is this Pulpute?
Sometimes, the things you put in there, for some reason, like the server...
Sometimes it returns to the server for some reason.
What? It goes back to the server?
Pulpute! Yes, yes, yes!
Like "eh"... "pulpunte"...
Like "nezo".
I'll be back in a minute...
I'll be right back.
I wonder if it's here.
I think it's here.
It's here...
Here it is!
By the way, the udon
I mean...
It's like this!
It's soft, delicious, and soft. I'd like to try it, but it's expensive because it doesn't have a firm texture.
I'd like to try it. I heard it's called "marten." Usually, over here, it's called "tempro.
But in Fukuoka, marten is called satsu-mage.
Like "jakoten.
Yes, yes, yes.
I see.
It's a kind of "satsumage" or "satsumage. Enjoy yourself.
All they do is eat.
Really.
I like croquette. I put croquette on soba noodles.
Korokke Soba I put croquette on Soba first, and I pinged Korokke Soba.
I like croquettes, but when I tell my partner about it, he says, "I don't know what you mean!
I'm sure it's true that croquettes are a bit of a joke.
You're right, Croquettes is a bara kale.
That's right.
That's it.
That...
A little bit.A little.
But it's so familiar.
Me too... and that's why we're always eating.
That's exactly how it started.
There used to be a place at Mitaka Station...
I think it's called "box noodles" now.
Oh!
The famous Hakone Soba.
That's where it was.
I think...
My memory's a little hazy.
It was a long time ago.
Whenever I was waiting for the bus or had some free time, I'd go in there and eat there.
I was probably still in elementary school or junior high at the time.
I was still in elementary school or junior high, so I had more money than I could spare.
I was blowing my nose over a 10,000 yen difference just now.
Like this...
After I was tired, I wiped it clean and blew my glasses for 15,000 yen.
I can't do that, it'll make them dirty.
but you see, there was the first one by the side, and then the highest one by the side...
That's right.
It was the first soba I ever had, and it was the only one I ever ate.
I knew it was only 150 yen back then.
No, those were the days.
That was around 1960.
No, that was a while ago.
It became expensive.
Since the 1950s.
Croquette noodles were about 150 yen, and croquette noodles were about 170 yen.
I've always wanted to have that one that's a grade higher.
If it's a croquette, that kid can eat it.
I'm sure he can eat a croquette... That's right... that's all I ate.
I can't do it. I've always done it.
So when I ate croquette soba for the first time...
I became an adult.
By the way, I wasn't that tall back then.
That's why you made it for adults.
That's why it looks like this.So, you know, it's like this.
Mini-master. I can't drink the soup because the bowl is too heavy to hold.
That's cute! I remember that.
That bowl of soba is surprisingly heavy.
I've been going to stand-up noodle shops lately.
It stands out.
Of course. It doesn't stand out.
It's really good... because it's cheap and fast.
That's why I go to standing-only noodle shops in train stations.
No image. No image at all.
That standing-only noodle shop has changed in the last few years.
They used to cater to morning businessmen and that kind of tag, but in the last few years they've realized they have to cater to female customers, so they've perfected their own restaurants.
I had to bring in female customers in the last years, and that's why my store is not so popular any more.
The first thing to do is to make sure that you have a good selection of products and services.
I'll let you try the grilled pork with yuzu.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to have a little bit of yuzu in there, but it's a good idea to have a little bit of yuzu in there too.
I'm just eating buckwheat noodles... or is that Hoshina eating buckwheat noodles?
I can't picture it at all.
I can't imagine it.
Oh no!
You're right...
There's something like that too...
Yes, I do.
That's why
I don't know... I don't know... I'm just trying to get a live feed.
I'm sorry, I'm just...
I got caught up in eating.
I haven't eaten.
So this is Shift Hoshina.
It's been a while since I've eaten. I wish I could get a shift.
It's been a while since I ate sushi standing up like this.
I heard there's a fish bar in there... but it looks like they're going to give us a loss... so if you put in a little more... there's a Thai chazuke restaurant that looks like it was built recently.
Eat there.
I thought the Thai chazuke was a little heavy.
So I went for the Thai tsukeme.
Then, I don't know if there were too many customers yet, but...
I don't know if they had many customers yet, but they suddenly offered me shaved ice.I got shaved ice, suddenly.
I got shaved ice!
You've got to be kidding me!
I'm lucky! I know I'm standing around saying that, but that's not true.
I don't really care... but I'm fine... just eat it.
I'm sure you'll find some in the city, but not at all.
We went there with the family the other day.
We went to Nagano and ate a lot of standing-only buckwheat noodles.
I like it only in summer.
I think it's only available in summer.
It's cold soba with tofu on top.
It's cold soba with a block of tofu on top.
I love it!
I don't know what it tastes like, but it's just tofu and soba.
I don't know what it tastes like, but it's like eating tofu and soba together
I'm glad you didn't say no.
I'm glad you didn't say no. But if you mix it in, if you mix it with the first one that came in, it becomes a little, well, I don't know how to put it, a little dirty, you know?
For example, tuna and natto (fermented soybeans with tuna), if you mix them together, they become sticky and soggy.
You have to mix it. You have to mix it.
That's right.
But if you get a rocket out of it, it's the best...
That's true. From a TV point of view. It's a bit of a TV thing, isn't it? Mixture of things.
Dangerous mixture.
It tastes good. Really tasty.
It's delicious.
So, this week is a little bit unusual.
I've received so many letters about food that I've only talked about food this week.
All we talk about is food and sauna.
Food and sauna... yes, that's right.
Did you do anything else?
You made me coffee, didn't you?
I asked her to make me some coffee.
I made him coffee, too.
Right...
Master Sarpon Ebinaka's Kombande Bone, from the Amasara series, soul food from his hometown of Numazu, Shizuoka... They bake them until crispy and then boil them, so they have a mysterious crunchy texture, somewhere between grilled gyoza and sui-gyoza!
Interesting!
So I had it with soy sauce, homemade mustard oil, and a dash of chili pepper.
and homemade mustard oil, and a dash of chili pepper!It was also served with a dash of chili pepper!
Voluptuous and juicy!
Like this.
It's stuffed!
Wow, it looks so delicious!
It's so stuffed!
I can't get enough of it!
I think it's a side rice dish... and you can eat it with rice and dumplings... but it's delicious even with the convenience of rice...
I'd love to eat gyoza.
I want gyoza.
Gyoza set menus?
Well...
It's an old story again.
We're on a loop.
You keep looking at food and talking about the past.
Gyoza and set menus reminded me of...
When I was a student...
You didn't have any money.
Now I have money.
Blow your nose with 10,000 yen bills
Blow your nose with an 80,000 yen bill
I blow my nose with a 4,000 yen bill
But I can't use a 1,000 yen bill to blow my ass...
I don't use it.
Not that much.
There was a guy I used to be friends with at the time who didn't have any.
He started working at a Chinese restaurant.
He said, "You know, Chinese restaurants have a lunch break around noon and a two or three hour break before dinner.
Usually it's just gyoza and rice.
But he made it first and served it to me.
It's so good, isn't it?
You used to eat them.
I was really hungry at the time.
I didn't have anything to eat.
With a cane.
Excuse me.
Please call it "my itinerary" for the gyoza set meal.
I'm glad you abbreviated it... because after we ate the dumplings and rice, you gave me that Chinese soup-like thing.I'm glad you abbreviated it so easily, because the older guy gave me some dumplings and that Chinese soup-like thing after rice.
I'm going to go now, I've got a cat's tongue and it's easy to say "fartch"!
It's so easy to say "fartch"!
It's easy to say "fartch" and it's just like that...
I put a little bit of gyoza sauce on the rice and let it bounce around a bit. I don't know, I like that after something like that, don't you guys! I don't know!
Aren't they huge?
You're awesome.
Shut up!
No, no, no, no, no, no, it's really weird.
You know, I used to eat unagi once.
There's sauce under the eel and the sauce and rice... it's so good!
Like, once I had that eel with sauce and rice on it.
It's not good at all!
It's someone's mystery... that's why it's grilled eel.
That taste that blended in.
That's right. That's what we're doing.
It's the same with yakiniku, too, with dumplings and meat.
It's like a waste of time and energy.
It's just a little too much joy.
It's been going on all week. That's all there is to it!
Well, well, well, that's how it's been, isn't it?
I'm sure you all enjoy food every day, so when you eat good food, it makes you happy, right?
So, I'm not going to tell you anything about Marge.
I don't have any more news to tell you...
That's right!
I'm wearing the long-sleeved shirt Hoshino gave me, by the way.
It has Hoshino's picture on it.
Thank you very much!
From a distance, it looks like a stylish T-shirt.
Please wear that one again.
And moreover...
I didn't give out T-shirts but penlight goods... so please wear that and come again.
I'm not wearing a T-shirt but a penlight... so I'm a big fan of your T-shirt... and I was thinking... wait a minute!
I can't keep up with you in such a hurry!
I can't keep up with you.
I'll break my heels.
It's a girl!
I'm in too much of a hurry.I'm in too much of a hurry.
I see. I see.
Oh, yeah.
I got a lot of pictures.
I got a lot of pictures of the Oyama song.
They're all great pictures.
So, in terms of Mt. Daisen, that means two weeks from now? Yes, that's right.
Then let's show them to you.
It's a really good one. It was made just for this.
It would be fun to hold a rock festival around Mt. Daisen, which I imagined on my own, like Fuji Rock.
I took the liberty of designing a t-shirt that says "Daisen Rock Festival 2023" and made it up myself.
It's a virtual festival. It doesn't really exist, but it's high quality enough to really exist.
I'm going to play a song about Oyama that will appear on this t-shirt, so please look forward to it.
If anyone wants one, I'll sell it for about 8,000 yen.
Isn't that expensive?
Expensive!
My birthday T-shirt is expensive.
You're right.
The one I want is very high quality.
Is there a picture on it?
I'm going home early to eat because I'm having too much meth-terrorism.
I'm looking forward to my birthday!
Let's eat!
Eat, eat, eat!
You know what's good about dinner?
Or have someone cook for you.
Even if it's at a restaurant.
It makes you really happy.
Thank you very much.
I'd love to see you at the TV store.
It's 8,000 yen.
That's too expensive.
It's about 8 times the price.
Fifty percent.
There are people who will buy it.
Someone who'll buy it? No? No? That's the price.
Don't buy it?
No, don't buy it.No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You mean buy it?
And Moshiki-san wants to make it on order!
Orders! Let's lower the price!
No, no, no, no, but, you know, capitalism!
If there is someone who will buy it...
No! I won't let you sell it!
No sale!
Stable, seriously!
What brand T-shirt?
You should put something like Chanel around here!
No, no, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
On the contrary, on the contrary.
I'll be back next week with a live broadcast.
I'll be back next week.
I'm going to say xx, right?
I'm going to be the official "x Japan" of Japan.
I'm not sure if it's a "Japan" or not, but I'm sure it's a "Japan"...  I'm going to tweet something. Master's account, oh! I'm looking forward to it. So, see you next week.
Thank you very much for this week.
YOU